EDUARDO SILVA

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Address: Cambridge, Cambridgeshire,

United Kingdom

Telephone: +44 (0) 7387771879

Email: gestoreduardoleon@gmail.com

EDUCATION

UNIP Universidade Paulista - Brazil

2015 - 2016

Studied Economics

Otoniel Mota - Brazil

1997 - 2014

FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT SKILLS

CSS





JAVASCRIPT – Still Studying the Course



FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT **EXTENSIONS AND TOOLKIT**

BOOTSTRAP





SKILLS

Attention to Detail





Organization



Working under pressure



LANGUAGES

Portuguese and English

WEBSITE AND PORTFOLIO LINK

www.eswebdevelopers.com

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a hard-working and self-motivated individual who is a fast learner. I have 1 year of experience in front-end development, with the hope to learn back-end development in the near future. This will allow me to become a full-stack developer. I enjoy doing the front-end development as it has allowed me to be innovative and creative in my projects.

EMPLOYMENT

Heraeus Noblelight- Cambridge (Product Operator)

JAN 2022 - PRESENT

Key responsibilities

- Fill the lamps with the correct gas
- Analysing the lamps to see if they are in the good condition
- Training new staff
- Managing a team of 2 person
- Cleaning the lamps with fire to avoid dust
- Looking for lamps that are faulty
- Working overtime to ensure we meet deadlines
- Assisting my colleagues whenever possible

Ede and Ravenscroft - Cambridge (Product Assistant)

SEPT 2021 - JAN 2022

Key responsibilities

- Cleaning the hats and gowns so that they are ready for the next graduation ceremony
- Organisation of the working area
- Maintaining cleanliness of working area
- Looking for hats and gowns that are faulty
- Training new staff

Rosie's Lunch Box - Cambridge (Café Helper)

MARCH 2020 - SEPT 2021

Key responsibilities

- Serving the customers their food and drinks
- Providing friendly and attentive service
- Assisting in preparing the food and drinks for the customers
- Assisting the business owner with organising the kitchen
- Maintaining the café cleanliness
- Stock checks
- Cashing up at the end of the day

Freeway Shoes - Brazil (Shop Assistant)

MARCH 2019 - MARCH 2020

Key responsibilities

- Welcoming customers to the store
- Helping customers finding the shoes they would like
- Providing recommendations to customers and advising on what shoe would best suit them
- Maintaining the organisation of the shoes in the stock room
- Assisting my colleagues whenever possible